Guide to the Time Inc. Corporate Public Affairs Department Records 1945-2000 (bulk 1959-1996) MS 3009-RG 19
New-York Historical Society
- Series VII. Exhibition Files from the Reception Center, Exhibit Hall, and Exhibition Center, 1949-1972; 15.5 Linear feet in 8 record cartons and 5 flat boxes
  - Subseries VII.C. Recurring Exhibitions Files, 1949, 1961-1970; 7.83 Linear feet in 3 record cartons and 2 flat boxes
    - The Sistine Chapel: General Files, 1958-1970 (Offsite-box 4053, Folder 10-12)
    - The Sistine Chapel: Floor Plans and Wall Text, 1961 (Offsite-box 4055, Item 10-17)
    - The Sistine Chapel: Floor Plans: Lobby, 1961 (Offsite-box 4055, Item 1-9)
    - The Sistine Chapel: Life Article, 1949 (Offsite-box 4055, Folder 1)
    - The Sistine Chapel: Music, 1962 (Offsite-box 4056, Folder 1-2)
      1 audiotape reel (endless tape): analog, 7 1/2 ips; 5 1/4 in., 1/4 in. tape. On container label: "Time & Life Easter Music. Sistine Chapel. 3/13/62. 7.5ips. Repaired 4/1/70."
      1 audiotape reel (endless tape): analog, 7 1/2 ips, monaural; 5 1/4 in., 1/4 in. tape. On container label: "W.O.#: R-28788" and "Product: Time & Life Easter Show."
      1 audiotape reel (endless tape): analog, 7 1/2 ips, monaural; 5 1/4 in., 1/4 in. tape. On container label: "W.O.#: R-28186" and "Product: Time & Life Easter Show."
    - The Sistine Chapel: Narration, 1968 (Offsite-box 4056, Folder 3-7)
      2 audiotape cartridges (Fidelipac cartridge): analog; 6 7/8 x 6 in., 1/4 in. tape. On label: "Easter ___. [Repair] 3/27/68."
      2 audiotape cartridges (Fidelipac cartridge): analog, 7 1/2 ips; 6 7/8 x 6 in., 1/4 in. tape. On label: "Sistine Chapel."
      1 audiotape cartridge (Fidelipac cartridge): analog, 3 3/4 ips; 6 7/8 x 6 in., 1/4 in. tape. On label: "Easter Narration. Sistine Chapel."
      3 audiotape cartridges (Echo-matic II self threading): analog, 3 3/4 ips; 5 x 3 1/2 in., 1/4 in. tape. On label: "Time, Inc. Exhibition Hall. Easter Show."
    - The Sistine Chapel: Photographs of Artwork, circa 1961 (Offsite-box 4055, Folder 2)
    - The Sistine Chapel: Transparency, circa 1961 (Offsite-box 4055, Item 18)
    - The Sistine Chapel: Wall Text, 1962 (Offsite-box 4056, Folder 8-9)
      Includes audiovisual material along with wall text labels.
      1 audiotape reel: analog; 5 in., 1/4 in. tape. On label: "Culture."
    - The Sistine Chapel: Wall Text, circa 1962 (Offsite-box 4057, Item 1-9)
- Series VIII. Time Life International/Corporate International Files on Exhibitions and Contests, 1959-1971; 3.1 Linear feet in 3 record cartons and 1 document case
  The management of the offsite and traveling exhibitions and loans started with Ed Lumsden and Jim Alberse in the promotion office of Time Life International (TLI). TLI became Corporate International in 1968 with Alberse in the public affairs office continuing management along with his assistant Jeanne Kerr. By 1969, Corporate International no longer existed as a department, and Alberse and Kerr transferred to Corporate Public Affairs still overseeing the international exhibitions and loans.
  Exhibitions in this collection were shown internationally and were either organized by Time Inc. or included loans from its collection. Exhibitions were to promote Time Inc. and its publications on an international scale or to promote specific aspects such as a new international publication like Life South Pacific or Life Asia. Based on the creators of the records, these exhibitions were managed separately from those shown in the Reception Center or Exhibition Center in the Time & Life Building, although some exhibitions were shown both onsite and traveled.
  Records include requests for photographs from Time Inc.'s collection; requests for rights to reproduce photographs taken by photographers working for Life to use in exhibitions; requests from the United States Information Agency (previously United States Information Service) for Time Life International to prepare exhibitions for it such as American Arts and Skills and the Shelburne Museum; memoranda and correspondence regarding installation and shipping; exhibition catalogs, guides, and brochures; news clippings; and some photographs of installed exhibits. The records are primarily from Jim Alberse and Jeanne Kerr with some from Ed Lumsden.
  Organized alphabetically by topic.
  - Exhibitions: Miscellaneous, 1965-1971 (Offsite-box 2324, Folder 1)
    Includes Life photograph loans, proposal for exhibits to show at the Time and Life Building, and a request to use the Time Inc. 40th anniversary film
  - Exhibitions: Alfred Eisenstaedt, 1968 (Offsite-box 2324, Folder 2)
    1 film reel; 16mm. On container: "Mr. O'Callaghan. Life/Time D. Jones. TV Channel 7 Brisbane. News Coverage '68. Eisenstadt exhibition."
    1 film reel; 16mm. (1 min., 12 sec). Label: "NLQ 539 Press Pix." On container: "Q'Land. Aust. B'Cast Commission Brisbane. T.V. News Film Coverage Eisenstadt Exhibition April 23, 1968."
  - Exhibitions: American Arts and Skills, 1959-1962 (Offsite-box 2324, Folder 3-4)
  - Exhibitions: American Arts and Skills [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R26)
  - Exhibitions: Eliot Elisofon, 1967 (Offsite-box 2324, Folder 5)
    Loans of Elisofon's photographs for an exhibition in Japan.
  - Exhibitions: Gordon Parks, 1966-1968 (Offsite-box 2324, Folder 6-10)
    Loans of Parks's photographs for a traveling exhibition and for Photokina.
  - Exhibitions: Herald Tribune Photographs, 1962-1963 (Offsite-box 2324, Folder 11)
  - Exhibitions: Illuminations of Fifty Great Paintings, 1959-1962 (Offsite-box 2324, Folder 12-17)
    A traveling exhibition produced by Life.
  - Exhibitions: Illuminations of Fifty Great Paintings, circa 1959-1971 (Offsite-box 2325, Folder 1-4)
  - Exhibitions: Illuminations of Fifty Great Paintings: Audiotape, circa 1959 (Offsite-box 4146, Item 1)
    Contains audiovisual material.
    1 audiotape reel: analog; 10 1/2 in., 1/4 in. tape. On container: "Tape on Illuminations 45 min-1 hr. Describes process, artists and paintings. Used in Los Angeles County Museum via walkie-talkie."
  - Exhibitions: Paul Hogarth, 1967-1968 (Offsite-box 2325, Folder 5)
    Loan of Hogarth's photographs for an exhibition at the Royal College of Art in London.
  - Exhibitions: Sony Tokyo, 1966 (Offsite-box 2325, Folder 6)
  - Exhibitions: Thirty Years of Life, 1966-1968 (Offsite-box 2325, Folder 7)
    Shown in Australia to promote Life South Pacific.
  - Exhibitions: Time Cover Art Show to Canada, 1968-1970 (Offsite-box 2325, Folder 8)
  - Exhibitions: Treasures from Poland, 1967 (Offsite-box 2325, Folder 9)
    An exhibition that Time Inc. attempted to borrow through the American ambassador to Poland for the Time Inc. Exhibition Center.
  - Exhibitions: Shelburne Museum, 1967-1971 (Offsite-box 2325, Folder 10)
  - Life en Español Writing Contest: Prize Stories from Latin America, 1962-1966 (Offsite-box 2325, Folder 11)
  - Life en Español Writing Contest: Prize Stories from Latin America [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R26)
  - Life en Español Writing Contest: Secret Ceremony, 1969-1971 (Offsite-box 2325, Folder 12-14)
    Records are regarding an author's copyright concern involving a film based on a novel based on a story submitted to the contest.
  - Life en Español Writing Contest: Secret Ceremony, 1969-1971 (Offsite-box 2326, Folder 1)
  - Life en Español Writing Contest: Secret Ceremony [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R26)
  - Life International, 1961?, undated (Offsite-box 2326, Folder 2)
    Includes a film roll of a possible presentation titled The Promise and Purpose of Life international version and audiovisual material.
    1 audiotape reel (BASF): analog, 7 1/2 ips; 3 in., 8 cm. tape. On container: "Radio Spot. Life International 25 sec JW 6006 Track 10."
- Series IX. General Files, 1945-2000; 26.5 Linear feet in 26 record cartons including 35 reels of microfilm
  Corporate Public Affairs General Files include annual reports, press releases, dinner books, weekly news clippings, and administrative files. General Files refer to all Corporate Public Affairs records that were not clearly created by or transfered by one office or individual. Some items in the first four subseries may include an individual's name, usually James Pitt, Louis Slovinsky or Stan Kapner. Some materials are to and from Jeanne Kerr, initially a public affairs assistant and later director of corporate contributions.
  Organized into six subseries:
  Subseries IX.A. Administrative Files
  Subseries IX.B. Annual Reports
  Subseries IX.C. Dinner Books
  Subseries IX.D. Press Releases
  Subseries IX.E. Scrapbooks
  Subseries IX.F. Weekly News Clippings
  - Subseries IX.A. Administrative Files, 1963-1989; 18 Linear feet in 18 record cartons
    Administrative Files include material to educate Corporate Public Affairs on Time Inc. activities and to assist staff on writing press releases and other communications regarding the activities. Records include financial and security analyst meeting agenda; briefing books, president's speeches, photographs, and questions and answers for the stockholders' annual meetings; background information and progress updates on joint ventures; background information, fact sheets, and press releases on Time Inc. publications, public programs, and departments; magazine media and advertising kits; and news clippings.
    The administrative files are primarily from Slovinsky, but also include files or materials from Donald Wilson, Kerr, Pitt, Kapner, public affairs senior associate Ed Adler, and press information manager Michael Luftman. These files may have been inherited by Slovinsky, filed together by an office worker in Corporate Public Affairs prior to transfer to the Time Inc. Archives, or filed together by the Time Inc. Archives after receipt. For example, earlier Analyst Meeting and Stockholder Meeting files from Pitt were housed with later similarly titled files from Slovinsky. While the speeches folders have material similar to the Chief Speechwriter series, this material looks like it was collected by Slovinsky or a different part of Corporate Public Affairs and not the Chief Speechwriter.
    Items of interest include a 1970 plan for pre-recorded video; a 1972 title list for Time-Life Video; photographs of a 1972 stockholders meeting; and a collection of letters from a campaign by the striking workers of the International Paper Androscoggin Mill in Maine.
    Unreformatted audiovisual and digital material in the collection is not accessible.
    - Advertising Age: 100 Leading Advertisers, 1981-1988 (Offsite-box 2100, Folder 1-8)
    - Adweek, 1981-1982 (Offsite-box 2100, Folder 9)
    - American Television and Communications, Inc. (ATC): Graphic Standards Manual, 1986 (Offsite-box 1749, Folder 8)
    - American Television and Communications, Inc. (ATC): Knickerbocker Communications: General, 1979-1980 (Offsite-box 2506, Folder 13-14)
    - American Television and Communications, Inc. (ATC): Knickerbocker Communications: Franchise Proposal, 1980 (Offsite-box 2506, Folder 15)
    - American Television and Communications, Inc. (ATC): Knickerbocker Communications: Queens Franchise, 1979-1985 (Offsite-box 2506, Folder 16)
    - American Television and Communications, Inc. (ATC): Releases, 1977-1986 (Offsite-box 2507, Folder 1-5)
    - American Television and Communications, Inc. (ATC): Slides, undated (Offsite-box 2507, Folder 6)
    - Analysts Meetings, 1965-1971 (Offsite-box 1749, Folder 9-16)
    - Analysts Meetings, 1974-1985 (Offsite-box 1750, Folder 1-12)
    - Analysts Presentations, 1964-1980 (Offsite-box 1750, Folder 13-14)
    - Analysts Reports, 1970-1982 (Offsite-box 1750, Folder 15-21)
    - Analysts Reports, 1983-1987 (Offsite-box 1751, Folder 1-6)
    - Annual Meeting, 1986 (Offsite-box 3294, Folder 1-4)
      "Original Q&A" folder includes digital material:
      1 computer disc (floppy disk): 8 in.
    - Annual Meeting, 1987 (Offsite-box 3294, Folder 5-10)
      "Q&As Originals" folder includes digital material:
    - Annual Meeting, 1988 (Offsite-box 3294, Folder 11)
    - Board of Directors Meetings, 1963 (Offsite-box 1751, Folder 7-8)
    - Book-of-the-Month Club Newsletter: At Our Club, 1984-1986 (Offsite-box 3294, Folder 12)
    - Broadcast, 1969-1973 (Offsite-box 1751, Folder 9-10)
    - Cable, 1980-1984 (Offsite-box 1751, Folder 11)
    - Cable TV Advertising, 1980 (Offsite-box 1751, Folder 12)
    - CBS/Time Inc. Age Wave, 1989 (Offsite-box 2100, Folder 10)
    - Changes and Choices in Employee Benefits, 1987 (Offsite-box 2100, Folder 11)
    - Chicago: Building and Cover Show, 1978-1984 (Offsite-box 3294, Folder 13)
    - Chicago: Relocation: Books and Magazine/AFP Operations, 1985-1986 (Offsite-box 3294, Folder 14)
    - Corporate Aircraft, 1977 (Offsite-box 3294, Folder 15)
    - Corporate Articles: Examples of Time Inc. Magazines Cirticizing Time Inc. Products, 1987 (Offsite-box 3294, Folder 16)
    - Corporate Cultural Affairs News, 1983-1986 (Offsite-box 3294, Folder 17)
    - Corporate History: 1975-Present, 1985 (Offsite-box 3294, Folder 18)
    - Covering Note and Order Form for Annual Report, 1981 (Offsite-box 2100, Folder 12)
    - Covidea: General, 1985 (Offsite-box 1751, Folder 13-14)
      Covidea files contain material on a joint venture between Time Inc., AT&T, Bank of America, and Chemical Bank.
    - Covidea: Background Material, 1985 (Offsite-box 1751, Folder 15-16)
    - Covidea: Conference Calls of Communications Committee, 1985 (Offsite-box 1751, Folder 17)
    - Covidea: Heffron, Frank, 1985 (Offsite-box 1752, Folder 1)
    - Covidea: News Release Announcement, 1985-1986 (Offsite-box 1752, Folder 2)
    - Covidea: Q&A Development, 1985 (Offsite-box 1752, Folder 3)
    - Dallas Morning News, 1987 (Offsite-box 3295, Folder 1)
    - Direct Broadcast Satellite TV, 1983-1984 (Offsite-box 1752, Folder 4)
    - Earnings: 1981: Press Releases (Offsite-box 2100, Folder 13-20)
    - Earnings: 1981: Proxy Statement (Offsite-box 2100, Folder 21)
    - Earnings: 1981: Reports to Shareholders (Offsite-box 2100, Folder 22-24)
    - Earnings: 1982: Letter to Shareholders (Offsite-box 2100, Folder 25)
    - Earnings: 1982: Press Releases (Offsite-box 2100, Folder 26-34)
    - Earnings: 1982: Proxy Statement (Offsite-box 2100, Folder 35)
    - Earnings: 1982: Reports to Shareholders (Offsite-box 2100, Folder 36-38)
    - Edit Seminar, 1978 (Offsite-box 3295, Folder 2)
    - Financial: Invest in MGM, 1967 (Offsite-box 1752, Folder 5)
    - Fortune: Advertising, 1979-1980 (Offsite-box 1752, Folder 6)
    - Fortune: Circulation, 1987 (Offsite-box 1752, Folder 7)
    - Fortune: Edit Information, 1977 (Offsite-box 1752, Folder 8)
    - Fortune: Facts, 1983 (Offsite-box 1752, Folder 9)
    - Fortune: First Cover Photo (copy), undated (Offsite-box 1752, Folder 10)
    - Fortune: International, 1982 (Offsite-box 1752, Folder 11)
    - Fortune: Press Releases, 1977-1987 (Offsite-box 1752, Folder 12)
    - Fortune: Publicity, 1982 (Offsite-box 1752, Folder 13)
    - Grunwald, Henry: Biography, 1984-1987 (Offsite-box 1752, Folder 14)
    - Grunwald, Henry: Speeches, 1969-1985 (Offsite-box 1752, Folder 15-16)
    - Home Box Office (HBO): General Information, 1974-1982 (Offsite-box 2507, Folder 7-9)
      Includes promotional material, a handbook on pay television, and press releases.
    - Home Box Office (HBO): Affiliate Services, circa 1982 (Offsite-box 2507, Folder 10)
    - Home Box Office (HBO): Articles, 1977-1984 (Offsite-box 2507, Folder 11-12)
    - Home Box Office (HBO): AT&T, 1981 (Offsite-box 1752, Folder 17)
    - Home Box Office (HBO): Audience Research, 1982 (Offsite-box 2507, Folder 13)
    - Home Box Office (HBO): Censorship, 1983 (Offsite-box 2507, Folder 14)
    - Home Box Office (HBO): CBS and Columbia Joint Venture Press Release and Q&A, 1983 (Offsite-box 2507, Folder 15)
    - Home Box Office (HBO): Columbia Pictures Industry, Inc. and Tri-Star Pictures Renegotiation, 1985 (Offsite-box 2507, Folder 16)
    - Home Box Office (HBO): First Amendment Information Kit, 1983 (Offsite-box 1752, Folder 18)
    - Home Box Office (HBO): Getty Oil Company and Premier Lawsuit, 1981 (Offsite-box 2507, Folder 17)
    - Home Box Office (HBO): Inside HBO: George Mair book, 1985 (Offsite-box 2507, Folder 18)
    - Home Box Office (HBO): Los Angeles Times Corporate Profile of HBO, 1983 (Offsite-box 2507, Folder 19)
    - Home Box Office (HBO): Obscenity, 1983 (Offsite-box 2507, Folder 20)
    - Home Box Office (HBO): Personnel, 1977-1984 (Offsite-box 2507, Folder 21)
    - Home Box Office (HBO): Photographs of People at Work, circa 1980 (Offsite-box 2507, Folder 22)
    - Home Box Office (HBO): Press Releases, 1980-1986 (Offsite-box 1752, Folder 19-24)
    - Home Box Office (HBO): Statement on Joint Venture by Four Movies Companies and Getty Oil Company, 1980 (Offsite-box 2507, Folder 23)
    - International Paper: Striking Workers' Letters, 1987 (Offsite-box 3295, Folder 3-4)
    - Magazine Development Fact Sheet, 1984-1987 (Offsite-box 1752, Folder 25)
    - Magazine Group Forums, 1986-1987 (Offsite-box 2507, Folder 25)
    - Magazine Issues (Newsletter of the Magazine Group), 1987 (Offsite-box 1752, Folder 26-28)
    - Magazines: General, 1974-1987 (Offsite-box 1753, Folder 1)
    - Magazines: Advertising, 1969-1988 (Offsite-box 2507, Folder 24)
    - Magazines: Fact Sheet, 1983-1988 (Offsite-box 2508, Folder 1-2)
    - Magazines: Max Plan, 1987 (Offsite-box 2508, Folder 3)
    - Magazines: Press Releases, 1980-1981 (Offsite-box 1753, Folder 2)
    - Manhattan Cable: Articles On, 1973-1989 (Offsite-box 2508, Folder 4)
    - Manhattan Cable: Press Clippings, 1976-1986 (Offsite-box 2508, Folder 5)
    - Manhattan Cable: Press Releases, 1980 (Offsite-box 2508, Folder 6)
    - Manhattan Cable: Programming, 1978-1980 (Offsite-box 2508, Folder 7)
    - Manhattan Cable At Work, circa 1980 (Offsite-box 2508, Folder 8)
    - Money: Awards, 1976-1987 (Offsite-box 1753, Folder 3)
    - Money: Edit Information, 1977 (Offsite-box 1753, Folder 4)
    - Money: Fact Sheet, 1981-1983 (Offsite-box 1753, Folder 5)
    - Money: House Organs List, 1979 (Offsite-box 1753, Folder 6)
    - Money: Logo, undated (Offsite-box 1753, Folder 7)
    - Money: Press Releases, 1978-1988 (Offsite-box 1753, Folder 8)
    - Money: Reprints, 1976 (Offsite-box 1753, Folder 9)
    - Money: Speakers, 1976 (Offsite-box 1753, Folder 10)
    - Moral Rights in Berne Copyright Convention, 1987 (Offsite-box 1753, Folder 11-12)
    - Moral Rights in Berne Copyright Convention [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R25)
    - New York Magazine Piece on Magazine Development, 1984 (Offsite-box 3295, Folder 5)
    - "New York Perspectives" Series, 1976-1979 (Offsite-box 3295, Folder 6-7)
    - Nexis, 1983-1984 (Offsite-box 1753, Folder 13-14)
    - Pay-Per-View Network, 1987 (Offsite-box 1753, Folder 15)
    - Personnel: Head Count, 1978-1981 (Offsite-box 2101, Folder 1)
    - Picture Policy Statement, 1977-1982 (Offsite-box 1753, Folder 16)
    - Pioneer Press, 1969-1984 (Offsite-box 2101, Folder 2)
    - PR Aids Bills and Orders, 1987-1989 (Offsite-box 2101, Folder 3-5)
    - Press Releases, 1982-1985 (Offsite-box 3295, Folder 9-11)
    - Press Releases, 1987 (Offsite-box 2101, Folder 6-7)
    - Silver Screen Pictures, 1983-1984 (Offsite-box 1753, Folder 17)
    - Society Pages of New York Times, 1980 (Offsite-box 3295, Folder 12)
    - Speeches and Remarks: Cave, Ray, 1985 (Offsite-box 2101, Folder 8)
    - Speeches and Remarks: Daniel, Carlyle C., 1983 (Offsite-box 2101, Folder 9)
    - Speeches and Remarks: Davidson, Ralph P., 1980-1987 (Offsite-box 2101, Folder 10-17)
    - Speeches and Remarks: Greene, Susan, 1985 (Offsite-box 2101, Folder 18)
    - Speeches and Remarks: Grunwald, Henry, 1987 (Offsite-box 2101, Folder 19)
    - Speeches and Remarks: Guttman, William, 1984 (Offsite-box 2101, Folder 20)
      Includes notes on the Gabe Perlman roast.
    - Speeches and Remarks: Heiskell, Andrew, 1966-1986 (Offsite-box 2102, Folder 1-4)
    - Speeches and Remarks: Heyworth, James O., 1983 (Offsite-box 2102, Folder 5)
    - Speeches and Remarks: Hiland, Bruce, 1985 (Offsite-box 2102, Folder 6)
    - Speeches and Remarks: Kelly, William, 1983 (Offsite-box 2102, Folder 7)
    - Speeches and Remarks: Luftman, Michael, 1985 (Offsite-box 2102, Folder 8)
    - Speeches and Remarks: Manley, Joan, 1986 (Offsite-box 2102, Folder 9)
    - Speeches and Remarks: Meyers, John A., 1968 (Offsite-box 2102, Folder 10)
    - Speeches and Remarks: Myhren, Trygve, 1981 (Offsite-box 2102, Folder 11)
    - Speeches and Remarks: Thomas, Richard B., 1982 (Offsite-box 2102, Folder 12)
    - Speeches and Remarks: Torello, Judy, 1986 (Offsite-box 2102, Folder 13)
    - Speeches and Remarks: Wilson, Donald, 1985 (Offsite-box 2102, Folder 14)
    - Spinoff Articles, 1983 (Offsite-box 3295, Folder 13)
    - Sports Illustrated: Advertising, undated (Offsite-box 1753, Folder 18)
    - Sports Illustrated: Press Releases, 1977-1989 (Offsite-box 1753, Folder 19)
    - Stock Listing on New York Stock Exchange (NYSE), 1964 (Offsite-box 1753, Folder 20-21)
    - Stockholders Annual Meetings, 1970-1975 (Offsite-box 1753, Folder 22-28)
      Materials from the annual meetings include briefing books, questions and answers, display material, press invitations, photographs of the meetings, and special meeting information.
    - Stockholders Annual Meetings, 1975-1979 (Offsite-box 1754)
    - Stockholders Annual Meetings, 1979-1982 (Offsite-box 1755, Folder 1-16)
    - Stockholders Annual Meetings, 1981-1983 (Offsite-box 2508, Folder 9-22)
    - Stockholders Annual Meetings, 1983-1987 (Offsite-box 2509)
    - Stockholders Annual Meetings [RESTRICTED], 1979 (Offsite-box R25)
    - Stockholders Approve Time's Acquisition of Temple, 1973 (Offsite-box 1755, Folder 17)
    - Subscription Television (STV), 1982-1983 (Offsite-box 1755, Folder 18)
    - Teletext, 1980-1983 (Offsite-box 1755, Folder 19-21)
    - Time: Ad Rate Cards, 1981 (Offsite-box 1756, Folder 1)
    - Time: Adler, Renata, 1986 (Offsite-box 1756, Folder 2-3)
    - Time: Advertising, 1977-1981 (Offsite-box 1756, Folder 4)
    - Time: Anniversaries, 1963-1983 (Offsite-box 1756, Folder 5)
    - Time: Newstours, 1981-1985 (Offsite-box 1756, Folder 6)
    - Time: Olympics, 1988 (Offsite-box 1756, Folder 7)
    - Time: Prospectus 1922 (copy), undated (Offsite-box 1756, Folder 8)
    - Time: Publicity, 1982 (Offsite-box 1756, Folder 9)
    - Time: "Technology and the Making of a Magazine": Special Ad Section, 1986 (Offsite-box 1756, Folder 10)
    - Time: Timeaid: Mexican Earthquake Relief, 1985 (Offsite-box 1756, Folder 11)
    - Time Canada, 1974-1984 (Offsite-box 1756, Folder 12-14)
    - Time Inc. Anti-Trust Conference, 1979 (Offsite-box 3295, Folder 14-15)
    - Time Inc. and Matsushita Electric, 1982 (Offsite-box 1756, Folder 15-19)
      Regarding the companies' agreement to co-develop hardware for use in Time Inc.'s teletext service.
    - Time Inc. in Profile, 1988 (Offsite-box 3295, Folder 16)
    - Time Inc.: Press Releases, 1980-1988 (Offsite-box 1756, Folder 20)
    - Time to Read, 1985-1988 (Offsite-box 1756, Folder 21-25)
    - Time-Life Broadcast: General, 1967-1971 (Offsite-box 1756, Folder 26)
    - Time-Life Broadcast: Proposal to Sell to McGraw-Hill, 1970-1972 (Offsite-box 1756, Folder 27)
    - Time-Life Broadcast: Proposal to Sell to McGraw-Hill [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R25)
    - Time-Life Video, 1970-1987 (Offsite-box 1757, Folder 1-2)
    - Tri-Star Pictures, 1982-1986 (Offsite-box 1757, Folder 3)
    - TV-Cable Week: General, 1982-1983 (Offsite-box 2102, Folder 15-16)
    - TV-Cable Week: Byron, Christopher, 1984 (Offsite-box 2102, Folder 17)
    - TV-Cable Week: Cable Magazine Project Statement and Q&As, 1982 (Offsite-box 2102, Folder 18-19)
    - TV-Cable Week: Cable TV Q&As, 1982 (Offsite-box 2102, Folder 20)